Guide to the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace pamphlet and microfilm collection, 1817-1950 MS2110
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Unbound pamphlets, 1817-1950; MS2110 Series 2; 47 Linear feet
  - "Creacion de un Orgaino Judiciario Internacional" ["Creation of an International Judicial Organ"], 1917 (Box 41, Folder 72)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-25, Author: Herrera, Miguel Juan
  - "Il Curso de la Universidad de Valladolid en Vitoria" ["The Curriculum of the University of Valladolid-in Vitoria-1947"] (Box 41, Folder 73)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-26, Author: Herrero, Alejandro
  - "La Crisis Actual Del Mundo" ["The Current World Crisis"], 1937 (Box 41, Folder 74)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-27, Author: Kunz, Josef L.
  - "El Derecho Intrnational en Espana" ["International Law in Spain"], 1905 (Box 41, Folder 75)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-28, Author: Labra, M. Rafael De
  - "Pacifismo Reformista Y Pacifismo Cientifico" ["Reformist Pacifism and Scientific Pacifism"], 1919 (Box 41, Folder 76)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-29, Author: Lasala, Sr. D. Manuel
  - "El Junsta y la Futira Organizacion Democratica del Estado" ["The Jurist and the Future Democratic Organization of the State"], 1943 ca. (Box 41, Folder 77)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-30, Author: Larin, F. Pablo
  - "El Concepto Moderno del Reconocimiento Internacional" ["The Modern Concept of International Recognition"], 1944 (Box 41, Folder 78)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-31, Author: Moreno, Isidoro Ruiz
  - "Reforma del Pacto de la Liga de Naciones Memorandum del Ministerio de Relaciones Exteriores del Peru" ["Reform of the Pact of the League of Nations"], 1936 (Box 41, Folder 79)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-32, Author: Ministerio de Relaciones Exteriores del Peru [Ministry of Foreign Relations of Peru]
  - "Discurso Inaugural de la duodecima Reunion Annual..." ["Inaugrual Address of the Twelfth Annual Meeting of teh Cuban Society of International Law"], 1929 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-33, Author: Ortiz, Dr. Rafael Martinez
  - "La Vida Y la Muerte del Heroe" ["The Life and Death of the Hero" (General Don Jose de San Martin)], 1933 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-34, Author: Otero, Jose Pacifico
  - "Bases de Derecho International Privado Para Una Ley de Introducion al Codigo Civil" ["Foundations of Private International Right through an Introductory Law to the Civil Code"], 1928 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-35, Author: Passe, J. Luis
  - "La Liga de las Naciones" ["The League of Nations" Bolivar-Napoleon-Wilson], 1919 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-36, Author: Quijano, Arturo
  - "Soberania Argentina en la Antacritida" ["Argentine Sovereignty in Antarctica"], 1949 ca. (Box 42, Folder 5)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-37, Author: Radio, Pedro
  - Republic of Chile Ministry of Foreign Relations ["Memorandum Containing Proposals for Reform of the League of Nations"], 1936 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-38, Author: Republica de Chile Ministerion de Relaciones Exteriores [typescript]
  - "Mexico en Ginebra" ["Mexico in Geneva"], 1932 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-39, Author: Robledo, Antoinio Gomez
  - "Campo de Nardos" ["Field of Spikenard"], 1926 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-40, Author: Rojas, Anstides
  - "Alocucion Pronunciada con Motivo de la Mocion Presentada a Efecto de Nombrar Socio Honorario de la Sociedad Mexicana de Geografia y Estadistica al Hon. Elihu Root..." ["Speech Given on the Occasion of Motion Presented to Name the Honorable Elihu Root an Honorary Associate of the Mexican Society for Geography and Statistics"], 1907 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-41, Author: Romero, Jose
  - "El General Leonidas Plaza" ["General Leonidas Plaza"], 1914 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-42, Author: Severol, Armando
  - "Sociedad Argentina de Derecho Internacional" ["Argentine Society of International Law"], 1927 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-43
  - "Bolivar Simbolo de America" ["Bolivar: Symbol of America, Liberator, Legislator, Apostle"], 1932 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-44, Author: Sociedad Bolivariana del Uruguay: Antuna, Jose G. [Bolivar Society of Uruguay]
  - "Sociedad Costarricense de Derecho Internacional" ["Costa Rican Society of International Law"], 1915 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-45, Author: Sociedad Costarricense de Derecho Internacional-Republica de Costa Rica [Republic of Costa Rica]
  - "Estatutos" ["Statutes fo teh Couban Society of International Law"], 1915 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-46, Author: Sociedad Cubana de Derecho Internacional
  - "Fundacion", 1914 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-47, Author: Sociedad Nicaraguense de Derecho Internacional ["Foundation of the Nicaraguan Society of International Law"]
  - "La Academia de Derecho Internacional de la Haya" ["The Academy of International Law at the Hague"], 1927 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-48, Author: Trelles, Camilo Barcia
  - "El Mar Como Factor De Protagonismo en la Politica Internacional" ["The Sea as a Leading Factor in International Policy"], 1945 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-49, Author: Trelles, Camilo Barcia [Editoria Universitaria Compostelana]
  - "Espana la O.N.U. la Doctrina Larreta y el Problema de la Intervencion" ["Spain the United Nations and the Larreta Doctrine, and the Problem of Intervention"], 1947 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-50, Author: Trelles, Camilo Barcia
  - "La Liga de las Naciones y los Grandes Problemas de la Politica Universal" ["The League of Nations and the Great Problems of Universal Politics"], 1928 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-51, Author: Ulloa, Alberto
  - "Cooperatus de Credito en los Estados Unidos" ["Credit Unions in the United States"], 1944 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-52, Author: Union Panamerican
  - "La Corte Permanetnte de Justicia International" ["The Permanent Court of International Justice"], 1934 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-53, Author: Urnitia, Francisco jose
  - "Los Problemas de la Humanidad y de la Historia y los Instrumentos y medios posibles par asolutcionarlos en America" ["The Problems of Humanity and the of History and the Possible Instruments and Means to Solve them in America"], 1936 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-54, Author: Vidaume, Alberto Sayar
  - "Ideano Internacional de Bolivar" ["International Ideology of Bolivar"], 1934 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-55, Author: Yepez, Jorge Villagomez
  - "Nuevas Orientaciones en Matina Constitucional" ["New Directions in Constituional Matters"], 1939 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    Subject: Spanish. Previous folder number: J-10-56, Author: Zamora, Clemente Juan
  - "Den 18 Maj 1939" ["18 May 1939"] (Box 42, Folder 25)
    Subject: Swedish. Previous folder number: J-11-1, Author: Bohtycheni, Oskar Ehlunds
  - "Den 18 Maj 1938" ["18 May 1938"], 1939 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    Subject: Swedish. Previous folder number: J-11-2, Author: Bohtycheni, Oskar Ehlunds
  - "Postens Benhandiling Under Frig..." ["The Post Office's Treatment During the War"], 1916 (Box 42, Folder 27 item 1)
    Subject: Swedish. Previous folder number: J-11-3, Author: Von Holstein, Lage Stael
  - "About Legal Status of Neutral Prizes and the 'Themis' Case", 1916 (Box 42, Folder 27 item 2)
  - "The American Peace Award Created by Edward W. Bok...to Achieve and Preserve the Peace of the World", 1923 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Previous folder number: A-4-4, Author:American Peace Award
  - "Constitution and Misc. Pamphlets", 1921-1922 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Previous folder number: A-4-89, Author:Women's International League for Peace and Freedom
  - "The Way to Peace - International Cooperation", 1931 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Previous folder number: A-5-89, Author:Holt, Hamilton
  - "Memorandum" [on research work/regional federalism], 1939 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    Previous folder number: A-5-193, Author:New Commonwealth Institute
  - "The Guidon: A Political Review", 1931 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    Previous folder number: A-5-305, Author:Women's National Republican Club, The
  - "International Christian Declaration", 1944 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    Previous folder number: A-6-56, Author:National Peace Council
  - "A New International Order: The Political and Constitutional Aspects", 1941 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    Previous folder number: A-6-57, Author:National Peace Council
  - "Unofficial British Peace Aims", 1942 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    Previous folder number: A-6-58, Author:National Peace Council
  - "St. Hilda's College, Oxford, July 11th to 14th 1941" (Box 47, Folder 9)
    Previous folder number: A-6-74, Author:Peace Aims Conference
  - "Watchman, What of the Night?", 1945 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    Previous folder number: A-6-93, Author:Swing, Raymond Gram
  - "My Peace Plan", 1945 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    Previous folder number: A-6-112, Author:Zerweck, Herman
  - "Questionnaire", 1938 (Box 47, Folder 12 item 1)
    Previous folder number: B-1-95, Author:.00001New Commonwealth Institute
  - "Questionnaire: Problems of Regional Federalism", 1939 (Box 47, Folder 12 item 2)
    Previous folder number: B-1-95, Author:.00002New Commonwealth Institute
  - "Belgian Curiosities of War", 1917 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    Previous folder number: B-2-11, no. 6-8, 10-17, 20
  - "Weekly Bulletin No. 1", 1916 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    Previous folder number: B-2-59, Author:Preparedness Information Service
  - "Reparations and War Debts" (Supplement to the Economist), 1932 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    Previous folder number: B-2-62
  - "Communication Concerning Economic Exploitation by Austro-Hungarian and Bulgarian Authorities on Occupied Serbian Territory", 1917 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    Previous folder number: B-2-66, Author:Serbian Legation
  - "Economic Mobilization of the United States for the War of 1917", 1918 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    Previous folder number: B-2-72, Author: U.S. General Staff War Plans Division.
  - "Atomic Energy - Or Security and Life?", 1946 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    Previous folder number: C-1-19, Author:Fairfield, Warren [typescript]
  - "Germany and Military Government Courts - 1946", 1947 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    Previous folder number: C-2-24, Author:Germany, Office of Military Government of [OMGUS]
  - "Military Government--Germany: United States Area of Control: Law #59: Restitution of Identifiable Property", 1945 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    Previous folder number: C-2-26, Author:Germany (Territory Under Allied Occupation)
  - "Address of Sir Richard Stafford Cripps", 1948 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    Previous folder number: C-4-36, Author:British Information Service
  - "The Army at War: Tunisia", 1943 ca. (Box 47, Folder 22)
    Previous folder number: C-4-37, Author:British Information Service
  - "Voice of Victory: The Battle of Egypt", 1943 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Previous folder number: C-4-38, Author:British Information Service
  - Conference on the Causes of War, [Programs 1,2,4-15], 1925-1940 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Previous folder number: C-4-78
  - "How to Save the Starving Children of Europe Without Aiding the Enemy, from the "The American Friend", 1943 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    Previous folder number: C-4-146, Author:Kershner, Howard E.
  - "The Roosevelt-Churchill Declaration", 1941 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    Previous folder number: C-4-194, Author:National Peace Council
  - "Norway Fights!", 1942 ca. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Previous folder number: C-4-203, Author:Norwegian Information Service, The
  - "Report of Speeches and Discussions on the Contemporary Crisis-Economic and Social Policies-Germany and her Neighbors-Education and the Present Crisis-A New Political Order?-The Indian Problem", 1941 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    Previous folder number: C-4-210, Author:Peace Aims Conference
  - "Report of Speeches on 'The Shape of the New Europe'", 1941 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Previous folder number: C-4-211, Author:Peace Aims Conference
  - "Citizenship in Territories Annexed by Germans", 1943 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    Previous folder number: C-4-245, Author:United Nations Information Office
  - "The Dutch Bank-Note Decree", 1943 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    Previous folder number: C-4-246, Author:United Nations Information Office [typescript]
  - "The Framework of Banking in German-Occupied Eastern Europe", 1943 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    Previous folder number: C-4-247, Author:United Nations Information Office
  - "German Occupied Ukraine", 1943 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    Previous folder number: C-4-251, Author:United Nation Information Office
  - "The Ostland", 1943 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    Previous folder number: C-4-254, Author:United Nations Information Office [typescript]
  - "Economic Condition of Italy", 1944 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    Previous folder number: C-4-266, Author:U.S. War Department Bureau of Public Relations [typescript]
  - "Report of Allied Control Commission", 1945 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    Previous folder number: C-4-267, Author:U.S. War Department Bureau of Public Realtions Press OverBranch
  - "Notes on Memorandum on Equality Tribunal", 1936 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    Previous folder number: E-1-20, Author:Davies, David
  - "International Understanding and Goodwill Pamphlets", 1933 ca. (Box 48, Folder 16)
    Previous folder number: E-1-47, Author:International Relations Committee [typescript]
  - "The UNRRA-It's Structure, Programme and Possibilities", 1944 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    Previous folder number: E-1-65, Author:National Peace Council
  - "State Government", 1930 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    Previous folder number: G-3-15, Author:American Legislators Association, The
  - "The Churches and the World Economic Crisis", 1932 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    Previous folder number: H-1-23, Author:International Christian Social Institute
  - "Recent Geneva (Switzerland) Session of 'ECOSOC' Spurred Moves for Sounder Trade", 1948 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    Previous folder number: H-1-28, Author:Lorwin, Lewis L. (Reprint from Foreign Commerce Weekly)
  - "Remarks of Honorable Lynn J. Frazier at Proceedings of Unemployment Conference", 1932 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    Previous folder number: H-2-11, Author:Congressional Record
  - "Letter" (Workers of Great Britain to the Workers of Germany), 1908 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    Previous folder number: H-4-21
  - "Constitution", 1935 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    Previous folder number: I-7-8, Author:Institute of Higher International Studies
  - "Honor to George Washington", 1932 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    Previous folder number: I-8-4, Author:United States George Washington Bicentennial Commission
  - "Sermons on George Washington", 1932 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    Previous folder number: I-8-5, Author:United States George Washington Bicentennial Commission
  - "Circulares", 1914-1915 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    Previous folder number: I-9-6, Author:Dutch Anti-War Council
  - "25 Faar Oorlag aau den Oorlog" ["25 Year War Against War"], 1929 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    Previous folder number: J-2-1
  - "Rapport de la Commission Juridique sur L'avant-projet de Declaration des Droits de L'Homme" ["Report of the Juridical Commission on the Draft Plan of Declaration of Human Rights"], 1947 ca. (Box 48, Folder 28)
    Previous folder number: J-4-2, Author:Adademie Diplomatiquie International [International Diplomatic Academy]
  - "Les Cirmes de l'Allenmange sur Mer" ["German Crimes at Sea"], 1918 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    Previous folder number: J-4-136, Author:Millerand, a.: The French Maritime League
  - "Les Criminels de Guerre et le Nouveau Droit Penal, International Moyen Efficace Pour Assurer la Paix du Monde" ["War Criminals and the New International Penal Law, Effective Means to Assure World Peace], 1946 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    Previous folder number: J-4-196, Author:Sottile, Antoin, International Law Reveiw
  - "Geneve Siege de la Societe des Nations" ["Geneva: Seat of the Legue of Nations"], 1929 ca. (Box 48, Folder 31)
    Previous folder number: J-4-202, Author:Trag, Robert de
  - "Die Nobelpreistrager" ["The Nobel Prize Winners"], 1934 ca. (Box 48, Folder 32)
    Previous folder number: J-5-55, Author:Junk, Victor
  - "Neimero Unics a cua del comitats compilats da nada peretti e Giacsms Ferroni" ["For Alberico Gentili on the Tri-Centinial of his Death 1550-1608"], 1908 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    Previous folder number: J-7-10, Author:Peretti, Nafa and Giancomo Ferroni
  - Circulars in regard to application for the Nobel Peace Prize, 1917-1939 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    Previous folder number: CA-3-25, Author:Nobel Committee, English/French
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1942-1949 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    Previous folder number: CA-6-2, Author: American Friends Service Committee
  - The Roumanian Question in Transylvania and Hungary, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    Previous folder number: CB-2-27, Author:Comnene, Nicholas
  - The Sanctions enforced by France and Belgium and the International Law, 1923 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    Previous folder number: CB-2-38, Author: Auswartiges Amt.
  - Romania before the peace conference - The Banat of Temeshvar, 1919 ca. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    Previous folder number: CB-2-76
  - Greece before the peace congress, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    Previous folder number: CB-2-88,Author: Venizelos, Eleutherios
  - Picture Charts of Britain at War, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    Previous folder number: CC-4-7, Author: British Information Service
  - Foreign Policy Association Publications, 1923-1948 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    Previous folder number: CE-2-17, Author: Foreign Policy Association
  - Japanese Invasion of Shanghai, January 28-March 7, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    Previous folder number: CF-3-24
  - The Italian Empire-Libya, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    Previous folder number: CF-7-2; Author:Italian Library of Information
  - Italian Foreign Policy, since 1870, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    Previous folder number: CF-7-4; Author: Italian Library of Information
  - The Mediterranean, Highway or Prison?, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    Previous folder number: CF-7-6; Author: Italian Library of Information
  - Development of Italian East Africa, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    Previous folder number: CF-7-7; Author: Italian Library of Information
  - Colonialism in Africa, 1940 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    Previous folder number: CF-7-8; Author: Italian Library of Information
  - The First Born Documents of Popular Constitutional Liberty, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    Previous folder number: CG-3-9; Author: Erk, Edmund Frederick [with printed Frederick Christmas Greeting]
  - Miscellaneous Publications, 1922-1940 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    Previous folder number: CG-3-17; Author: National Woman's Party
  - Proposal for an International Bureau of Moral Education, 1910 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    Previous folder number: CI-7-2; Author: International Moral Education Congress
  - Memoire de la population des communes de Dibra en Macedoire [Memorandum from the population of the communities of Dibra in Macedonia], 1919 ca. (Box 49, Folder 17)
    Previous folder number: CJ-4-17; Author: Bojinoff, W.[Location, Sofia?]
  - Greece before the Peace Congress (Box 49, Folder 18)
    Previous folder number: CJ-4-124b; [French]
  - Look [magazine], a contribution to the cause of peace, 1938 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Formerly folder A-5-139
  - Workmen's Peace Association and International Arbitration League, Report and balance sheet for year ending December 31, 1887., 1888 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Formerly folder A-1-13
  - Derocco, DJ, "La Baranya Serbo-Croate: Carte Ethnographique d' Apres les donnees Corrigees de la Statistique Officielle Mongroise de 1910" [map], 1919 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Formerly folder J-4-50
- Microfilm, 1847-1949; MS2110 Series 3; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains eighty-two reels of microfilmed monographs of about 600 pamphlets. Most are in foreign languages (French, German, Spanish).
  - Le Droit et la Guerre, vol. 1-2, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Dejongh, Charles: Location, Paris
  - Le Droit et la Guerre, vol. 3, 1917-1919 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - L'Assistance aux Prisonniers de Guerre..., 1924 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Author: Anthouadr, A: Location, Paris
  - Rapport... and Annexes... vol. 1-3,Album des Crime Bulgares, 1915-1919 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Comission Internalliee: Location, Paris
  - Les Violations des Lois de la Guerre par L'Allemagne, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Author: France. M. A. E: Location, Paris
  - A. E. Documents Diplmatiques 1860, 1861 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Documents Diplomatiques 1861, 1862 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Documents Diplomatiques 1866 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Documents Diplomatiques, Decembre 1873 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - D. D. Deuxieme Conference International de Paix 1907, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - D. D. Conference Navale de Londres 1908-1909 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - D. D. Convention D'Arbitrage Avec L'Angleterre, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - D. D. Accords Relatifs a la Mer du Nord, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Convention... entre la France et L'Espagne, 1885 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Author: France. Treaties: Location, Paris
  - D. D. Espagne, 1907, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Traite enter la France et la... Suisse, 1882 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - D. D. Indemnites Franco-Italienne, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - D. D. Saint - Siege, 1903 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - D. D. Affaires de Turquie 1900-1901, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - D. D. Affaires D'Orient 1875-1877 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - D. D. Affaires D'Orient. Congres de Berlin, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Commission Technique Europeenne, 1879 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - D. D. Navigation du Danube, 1883 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - D. D. Affaires D'Orient... Traite Greco-Turc, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - D. D. Affaires D'Orient. Emprunt de L'Indmnite..., 1898 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - D. D. Arrangement Financier Avec la Grece..., 1898 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - D. D. Affaires D'Orient Autonomie Cretoise..., 1898 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - D. D. Affaires D'Orient, Affaire de Crete..., 1897 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - D. D. Affaires D'Orient, Affaire de Crete. Conflit Greco-Turc..., 1897 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - D. D. Affaires D'Orient. Autonomie Cretoise, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - D. D. Affaires D'Orient. Evacuation de la Crete, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - D. D. Affaires de Crete 1904-1905 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - D. D. Question de la Reconaissance de la Roumanie, 1879-1880 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - D. D. Affaires de Mcaedoine 1902-1903 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - D. D. Affaires de Macedoine 1903 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - D. D. Affaires de Macedoine 1903-1905 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - D. D. Affaires de Macedoine Elevation, 1907 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - D. D. Negotiationes Relatives au la... Grece... vol. 1-2, 1879-1880 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - D. D. Affaires de Grece en 1880, vol. 1-2, 1881 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - D. D. Affaires de Mascate. Commerce des Armes, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - D. D. Affaires du Haut-Mekong, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - D. D. Affaires de Siam et du Haut-Mekong, 1896 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - D. D. Affaires de Siam, 1893 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - D. D. Affaires de Roumelie et de Grece, 1886 (Box 8, Folder 1)